[Song]
Hello, this is Pavalisa Chumwikran, Chief
Marketing Officer of FWD Life Insurance.
[Song]
Regarding FWD, our brand...   Our
great success is mainly due to
our outstanding strategy.   What makes it stand out
? Firstly,
our strategy is adaptable.
At all times, to meet the needs of...
Consumers have changed, that's point number 2.
Our strategy is different...   It's
different because we use it for...
Positive energy is used in terms of inspiration
or a positive attitude in
communication.  In brand building, which is done...   It
makes us different from other people, and...
Finally, I must say that our strategy
is a combination of both science and economics.   The
combination involves integrating technology with
creativity in communication.    And then we
communicate the brand
[with music]. We
must say that we are very confident that in the
next 12 months, our FWD life insurance brand
will be strong and grow.   We are
continuously growing because we are focused.   We are committed to
making our brand the top
of mind for Thai consumers.
[Song]
Receiving this award for the second year in a row is
another source of pride for us.   In
our case, it's like a machine.   This guarantees the
success of our brand.
Winning an award from the brand is like a source of encouragement.
Yes, and it's also a driving force for everyone.
Our entire team is committed to creating...   We continue to
innovate and develop our brand without stopping.
Yes, that includes our desire to maintain standards.
Things on the roof too, please.
[Song]